Thank you for watching!
The kettle and the idol
Now, and secondly, exercise!
Yes, I know. Ever since I was a little girl, my family has been going out a lot,
I love physical activities, and in junior high school and elementary school, I loved physical education and classes so much that I looked forward to gym class and school lunches,
I'm also pretty good at sports,
I'm quite good at sports, so it's okay to be unequal!
Yes, I am. I think I'm probably a good athlete.
I did a 50-meter run with the members of the group before.
We did it as a group,
I came in first, ahead of Mirei.
I had an image that Mirei is athletic.
Mirei is really fast and athletic,
But I overtook her and came in first.
I'm fast now.
Yes, I am fast now.
Who is the slowest?
Is it your sister?
There is a girl who is riding this far.
Really? This far?
She was the slowest and ran at her own pace until the very end.
Is there such a thing as running at your own pace?
When we were running at the finish line, Kokubowino was laughing.
When we were really running hard to the finish line, Kokubowino was running with a smile on his face.
Oh, really?
That's how fast-paced he was.
Were you and Mirei already serious?
Yes, we were very serious.
By the way, did your time change?
Did your time change?
My time didn't change.
7.8 seconds?
That's fast.
7.8?
I ran a 6.9 in grade school.
That fast?
I've slowed down.
I think I'm a 7.8 for 50m.
6m is a real feat.
So from now on, I'm going to be in charge of the fastest in porn.
We have 5 young members and 5 older members.
I would like to have an athletic meet there.
Relay race
I'd like to see that.
I'd like to try it.
I'm looking forward to seeing what the older ladies will do when the younger members push up against them.
I wonder if that will be planned.
I'd love to see it.
Do you love to exercise and do you work out with your subordinates?
Clubs?
Yes, I do.
I did gymnastics in elementary school.
Really?
I started in the fall of the second grade.
I see.
I've been doing it for quite a while.
With ribbons and clubs and stuff.
Is there a connection to live performance?
It's just a whole different thing?
No, but we had a ballet teacher who came in for some of the physical exercises.
So we had a ballet instructor come in and teach us how to make our hands beautiful.
The angle of the hands.
And the angle of the face.
It's important to show off your body in body movement.
So it was important to show off your body maneuvering.
I think it is used in the live performance.
And also posture.
I've always had a hunched back.
I was always hunched over.
But thanks to physical exercises and ballet
But thanks to physical exercises and ballet, I think my hunchback is gradually getting better.
Yes, ma'am.
What is this program?
Mizucchi
Mamemabo
I'm sure you'll like it.
Mr. hy007
The End
This article was sent to you courtesy of Mr. No Nickname.
Thank you very much.